Guide to the Women in the Urban Crisis Records, 1969-1984 AIS.1985.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1969-1984; I.
  - Correspondence G-I, 1969-1984; 3.
    - I-Letters to Individuals, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Ida J. Brannen Wesleyan Service Guild of Warren, United Methodist Church, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - IMPACT, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Imperial Quality Horseshoes (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Improved Benevolent Protection of Elks (IBPOE), The Education Department of, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Infant Formula, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Information Volunteer Services of Allegheny County, 1970-1981 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Institute of Lifetime Learning, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Institute on Human Ecology of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Insurance: National Health Welfare Mutual Life (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - International Year of Disabled Persons, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Correspondence J-L, 1969-1984; 4.
    - J-Letters to Individuals, 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Jewish Chronicle, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Jewish Community Relations Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Job Advisory Service, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Job Advisory Service (Chatham), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Job Corp, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Joint Action in Community Service (JACS), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Joint Committee on Public Welfare, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Junior League of Philadelphia (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Junior League of Pittsburgh, 1970-1982 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Juvenile Justice Center of Pennsylvania, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - K- Letters to Individuals, 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Kane Hospital, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Kaufmann's, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - KDKA-TV, 1970-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Kellogg, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Keystone Christian, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - King Jr., Mrs. Martin Luther, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Martin Luther King Club at Larimer Elementary School, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Kingsley Association, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Kline, Caryl, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Know, Inc., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Koppers Company, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Kramer, Phyllis, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Kroger Company, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - L- Letters to Individuals, 1969-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Labor Department, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Lawrenceville Family Service, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - League of Women Voters, Allegheny County Council, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - League of Women Voters, Mt. Lebanon, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - League of Women Voters, Pittsburgh, 1969-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Leoni, Shellie, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Lesko, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Levinson Foundation, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Logan School Programs, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Louik, Michael- Assistant Attorney General, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Louise Child Care Center, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Lutheran Church Women of First Lutheran Church, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1969-1984; 5.
    - M- Letters to Individuals, 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Mackintosh-Hemphill Division, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Magic Carpet, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Manpower, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - March of Dimes, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Mayor's Task Force, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - McCloy Company, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - McGregor, Senator Jack, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Meals on Wheels, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Medical Committee for Human Rights, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Medical Eye Bank of Western Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Mellon Foundation, Richard King, 1970-1984 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Mellon National Bank, 1969-1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Mental Health Retardation Center, Inc.- Allegheny East, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Mental Health Retardation Citizen Advisory Board- Area 9C, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Mercy Hospital, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Meredith Broadcasting Corporation, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Merton Center, Thomas- Ministry for Justice Peace, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Metropolitan Pittsburgh Public Broadcasting, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Metropolitan Tenants Organization, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Michelson Advertising Agency, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Mini-Corporation Housing Association of Allegheny County, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Mobilization for Survival, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Mt. Lebanon Citizens for Community Relations, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Ms. Foundation for Women, Inc., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Multi-Senior Citizen Center, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - National Alliance of Businessmen, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL), Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1971-1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Legal Defense Fund, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Women's Axuliary, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - National Association of Negro Business Professional Women's Clubs, Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - National Association of Social Workers, Inc. (NASW), Southwest Pennsylvania Chapter, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - National Black Political Assembly, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - National Center for Voluntary Action, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing (NCDH), 1970-1981 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - National Committee on Household Employment, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - National Congress of Neighborhood Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, 1969-1984 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1969-1982 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - National Federation of Settlements Neighborhood Centers, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - National Health Service Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1969-1979 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - National Science Foundation, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - National Urban Coalition, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - National Welfare Rights Organization, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - National Women's Mailing List, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - National Women's Political Caucus, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - National Youth Pilgrimage, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Nationwide Communications, Inc., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - NBC Television Network, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Negro Education Emergency Drive (NEED), 1970-1981 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Neighborhood Legal Services Association, 1970-1982 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Neighborhoods for Living Center, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Neighbors in Need, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - New American Movement, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - New World National Bank, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - New York Life Insurance Company, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Nolan, The Honorable Thomas, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - North Park Transfer Station, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Northview Heights Resident Council, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Northwest Tenants Organization, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - O- Letters to Individuals, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Oakland News, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Oakland Women's Center, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Ohio Valley Provision Company, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - OIC International, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Open Doors for the Handicapped, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Operation Transit Awareness Campaign (TAC), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Operation Transportation, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ozanam, 1971-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence P, 1969-1984; 6.
    - P- Letters to Individuals, 1969-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Panel of American Women Human Relations Program, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Parents' League for Emotional Adjustment, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Parents School of Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh City Parents Teachers Association Mental Health Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Parents Teachers Association- Television Violence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Port Authority Transit, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Patients' Rights Program, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Peace and Freedom Center, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Penn Fixture Supply Company, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Penn's Southwest Association Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Penney, J.C., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Advisory Council for Vocational Education, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Association for Retarded Children, Inc., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Older Persons, Inc. (PAOP), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Board of Probation Parole, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania Civil Service Jobs, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania Coalition on Food and Nutrition, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Commission for Women, 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Community Affairs, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Education, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Justice, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Action-Zero Population Growth, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Council, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania Equal Rights Council, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania Health and Welfare Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania House Bills 2044 2340, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Pennsylvania Human Relations Commission, 1969-1982 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Pennsylvania Human Services Forum, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Pennsylvania Humanities Council, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Pennsylvania Interscholastic Athletic Association (PIAA), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Pennsylvania Mental Health, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Pennsylvania Milk Marketing Board, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Pennsylvania Negro Democratic Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Pennsylvania Nurses Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Pennsylvania Pretrial Justice Federation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Pennsylvania Program for Women and Girl Offenders, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Pennsylvania Public Health Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Pennsylvania Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Pennsylvania Secretary to the Department of Public Welfare, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Pennsylvania Senate, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Pennsylvania State Police, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Pennsylvania State University, Urban 4-H Nutrition Program, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Pennsylvania, Indiana University of, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Pennsylvania Women's Legislative Exchange, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Pennsylvania Women's Political Caucus of Allegheny County, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Pennsylvanians for the Preservation on Public Television, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Pennsylvanians for Women's Rights, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Peoples Gas Company, 1970-1984 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Philadelphia, City Personnel Department, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Philadelphia, City Police, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Pioneer Women Pittsburgh Council, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Pirates Wives, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Pitney-Bowes, Inc., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Pittsburgh Action Against Rape, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Pittsburgh Alliance for Displaced Homemakers, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Pittsburgh Area Pre-School Association, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Pittsburgh Area Religion and Race Council, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Pittsburgh Association for the Advancement of Women, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Pittsburgh Brewing Company, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Pittsburgh Building Construction Industry, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Pittsburgh Catholic, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Pittsburgh Child Guidance Center, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Pittsburgh City Commission on Human Relations, 1971-1981 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Pittsburgh City Council, 1971-1981 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Pittsburgh City Department of Personnel Civil Service, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Pittsburgh City Mayor, 1969-1979 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Pittsburgh City Parks and Recreation, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Pittsburgh Coalition on National Priorities, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Pittsburgh Committee for Human Rights, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Pittsburgh Community Leadership Coalition (PCLC), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Pittsburgh Conference of Jewish Women's Organizations, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Pittsburgh Council on Public Education, 1971-1983 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Pittsburgh Courier, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Pittsburgh Diocesan Council of Catholic Women, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Pittsburgh Federal Executive Board, 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Pittsburgh Forum, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Pittsburgh Free Clinic, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation, 1970-1983 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Pittsburgh History Landmarks Foundation, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Pittsburgh Housing Authority, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Pittsburgh Maulers, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Pittsburgh Model Cities Program, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Pittsburgh National Bank, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Alliance, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Alliance- Operation Partnership: Pittsburgh, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Pittsburgh Pastoral Institute, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Pittsburgh Presbyterian Society, 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Pittsburgh Press, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1973-1984 (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools Desegregation Project, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools- Parent Representative Section, 1979-1984 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Pittsburgh Public Schools- Summer Work Program, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Pittsburgh Radio Organization, Inc., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Pittsburgh Residential Manpower Center, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Pittsburgh Sisters' Council, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Pittsburgh Symphony- Women's Society, 1973-1982 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Pittsburgh Walk for Development, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Pittsburgh Women's Task Force, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Pittsburgh Working Women, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - "Pittsburgh Yes", 1972 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Planned Parenthood Center of Pittsburgh, 1970-1982 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Pleva, Mrs. William, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Point Park College, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Pornography, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Practising Law Institute, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Pre-trial Justice Federation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Private Line, undated (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Private Providers Pilot Project, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Program for Female Offenders, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Program Services Institute, Carnegie Library, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Program to Aid Citizen Enterprise (PACE), 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Project Equality, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Project Forward, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Project Pace Setter, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Public Affairs Committee of the Student Union Board Citizen Information Center, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Public Education Fund, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Public Management Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Public Relations Society of Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Public Service Materials Center, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence R-T, 1969-1984; 7.
    - R- Letters to Individuals, 1970-1984 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Rabbinical Association of America, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Rape Sexual Assault Center, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Recreational Opportunities Advancement Council, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Reizenstein Consortium, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Reizenstein, Mr. Louis, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Resources for Youth, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Retail Merchants Association, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Retired Executive Volunteers, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Retired Senior Volunteer Program, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Rhea's Bakery, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Robert Morris College, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Rodef Shalom Sisterhood, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Rodef Shalom Temple, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Rodman Street Baptist Church, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ruden and Finn, Inc., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - S- Letters to Individuals, 1970-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - St. Brigid-St. Benedict, The Moor Church, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - St. Francis General Hospital, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - St. Joseph's School, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - St. Margaret's Memorial Hospital, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - St. Mary of Mercy Church, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - St. Paul's Cathedral, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - St. Peter's Child Development Centers, Inc., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Salk Institute, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Sarah Mellon Scaife Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Schenley High School, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - School Volunteers Association of Pittsburgh, 1969-1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Company, 1969-1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Senate Bills, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Senior Citizens News, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Shady Lane School, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Sickle Cell Society, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - South Hills Association for Racial Equality (SHARE), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - South Hills Village Merchants Association (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - South Oakland Citizens Council, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - South Pittsburgh Consumers Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - S H Green Stamp Company, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Stanwix Autopark, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - State Committee Hearings, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - State Correctional Institution at Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - State Tenant Organization of Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Sterrett School Parents Club, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Stevens, Boycott of J.P., 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Stouffer's, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Student Coalition Against Racism, Univ. of Pittsburgh, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Superior Envelope Mfg. Corporation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Superjet Travel, Inc., undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Swan Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - T-Letters to Individuals, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Taft Broadcasting Company (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Talk Magazine, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Target '72, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Teacher Centers, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Teamsters' Local 249, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Terrace Village Health Center, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Third United Presbyterian Church, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Thorofare Markets, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Toner Institute, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Town Meeting, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Tuberculosis League of Pittsburgh, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Television Violence, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Correspondenc U-V, 1969-1984; 8.
    - Union National Bank of Pittsburgh, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Unitarians for Social Action, Unitarian Universalist Church of South Hills, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - United Family Services of Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - United Farm Workers, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - United Fund of Allegheny County, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - United Jewish Federation, 1969-1980 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - United Mental Health Services of Allegheny County, 1971-1981 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - United Methodist Women- Warren United Methodist Church, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - United Nations Association of Pittsburgh, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - United Nations Decade for Women, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - U.S. Government Census, 1977, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - United States Consumer Products, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - United States Department of Commerce, 1971-1979 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - United States Department of Health Education Welfare, 1973-1981 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - United States Department of Housing Urban Development, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - United States Department of Justice, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1969-1984 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - United States Department of State- Agency for International Development, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - United States Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - United States House of Representatives, 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - United States Marine Corps, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - United States Office of Emergency Preparedness, undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - United States President, 1971-1979 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - United States Secretary of Transportation, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - United States Senate, 1970-1979 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - United States Steel Corporation, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - United Steel Workers of America, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - United Methodist Women of Warren United Methodist Church, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - United Way, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - United Women's Cooperative (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Unity in Housing, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - University and City Ministries, 1970-1982 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - University of North Carolina, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1970-1984 (Box 5, Folder 93)